《诉讼双雄》前情提要
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
今早我们要和罗伯特·赞恩律所合并了
As of this morning, we're merging with Robert Zane.
我当时来的时候  你说我
When I came over, you said my name
首席翻译官
█ 网易见外
会成为下一个冠名合伙人
would be the one to go up next.
我向你保证  你会是下一个冠名合伙人
You have my word. Your name goes up next.
我取掉了子宫帽
I threw away my diaphragm.
首席校对官
人人译视界
·
人人
你要撤掉"守门员"了
You're pulling the goalie?
是的  路易  是的
Yes, Louis, I am.
我需要你去说服罗伯特·赞恩最大的客户
I need you to get Robert Zane's biggest client
翻译     arcadiachi  Alex  苏葵   小溪1120
卖掉他们的生产部门
to sell their manufacturing division.
这取决于谁真正管理律所
This is going to determine who runs the firm.
我需要你帮我度过这个关卡
I need you to come through for me on this one.
翻译     Giggles  斗斗  克里斯托啊托  大能  木浅
你们的客户就要关掉他们的制造部门
Your client is dropping their manufacturing division,
然后我们就可以开始在
and we can get back to the business of running this firm
校对     木浅
罗伯特·赞恩的指导下经营律所了
under the direction of Robert Zane.
你觉得我打不赢萨曼莎·惠勒吗
You think I can't take Samantha Wheeler?
我是觉得你好像说过不愿插手此事
I think you said you'd stay out of it,
时间轴     张小满   知之
我才不要替你通知你的队友
and I'm not going to help you tell your own team
你要架空他们
that you'll cut them out
就为了战胜萨曼莎·惠勒
just to get the better of Samantha Wheeler.
后期     斯人
我完成了你的要求  现在我有要求了
I did what you asked, and now I have something to ask.
-什么要求  -你知道我想要什么
- What's that? - You know what I want.
-萨曼莎  -罗伯特  我要当冠名合伙人
- Samantha. - Robert, I want name partner,
总监     木浅
今年之内就要
and I want it before the year is out.
你说如果我愿意承认
You said that I should come back
┌
┐
└
┘
人人影视官方客户端
唯一下载渠道
app.YYeTs.com
┌
┐
└
┘
你是对的  我就应该回来
when I was ready to admit that you were right.
要承认这点不容易  哈维
Takes a big man to admit that, Harvey.
-我的办公室  -怎么了
- My office. - What about it?
我想要回来
I want it back.
你无所畏惧的领导很乐意应允
Your fearless leader is happy to comply.
-希拉  这是干嘛  -一顿"权利之宴"
- Sheila, what is all this? - A power breakfast.
看上去太诱人了
And it looks delicious,
但你知道我早饭吃的都很简单
but you know I usually like to eat light in the morning.
-简单的一碗谷物早餐  -我知道  路易
- Just a bowl of Fiber One, or-- - Oh, I know, Louis.
我也知道你接管律所的日子可不普通
I also know the day you take control of the firm is no usual day.
在我接管什么之前
Before I take control of what now?
路易  你们律所刚刚合并  这意味着
Louis, you just merged, which means it's time
一位新的领袖即将诞生
for a new king to claim the throne.
希拉  如果我没理解错你的意思
All right, Sheila, if you're saying what I think you are,
哈维已经是经营合伙人了
Harvey's already managing partner,
而且赞恩正在觊觎他的位置
and Zane's going to fight to take it from him.
这也给了你从中竞争的机会
Which sets the table for you to take it from both of them.
路易  你有帝王之才
Louis, you're a king.
我们都应该对你顶礼膜拜
And we should all be kissing your ring.
希拉  你怎么会有这种想法
But, Sheila, where is all this coming from?
那是因为
It's coming from the fact that
哈维让你以一敌众
Harvey left you to fight off the hordes,
你竟然做到了  你赢了罗伯特·赞恩大军
and you did just that by subjugating the army of Robert Zane.
-好像确实是这样  -不是好像  路易
- I suppose I did. - No supposing, Louis.
你就是天神  维京天神
You're a god. A Viking god.
维京天神可以随心所欲
And Viking gods take what they want.
现在去吧  宣告你的领属
Now go in there, and claim what's yours.
我会  但在这之前我要宣告我的领属包括
I will, but not until I claim what's also mine--
时机不对
Not yet.
等你办完正事  我们下午再继续
Let's do it this afternoon, afterward.
到时我们再玩"经营合伙人和秘书"的游戏
Then we can play "Managing partner/secretary."
要是这样你到时候可有
In that case you'd better be ready to
好多的"工作"要做
take a whole lot of dictation.
我会准备就绪  你去吧
Oh, I will. Now go.
-我在这里静候佳音  -等着吧
- And return to me a king. - I know.
赞恩-斯佩克特-利特律所
-早上好  罗伯特  -哈维  我刚到
- Morning, Robert. - Harvey, I just got in.
-律所牌子不错  -很好  很高兴你喜欢
- The sign looks good. - Good, I'm glad you liked it.
你准备好了吗
You ready to do this thing?
如果你是说  我准备好成为经营合伙人了
If you mean, am I ready to get back to being a managing partner,
那毫无疑问
I sure as hell am.
那你就签好字
Then give me your John Hancock,
我去找路易  今天结束前
I'll get it to Louis, and you will officially be
你就是名副其实的经营合伙人了
the managing partner by the end of the day.
哈维·斯佩克特
Harvey Specter?
是我  这是我的合伙人  罗伯特·赞恩
That's right, this is my partner, Robert Zane.
迈克·罗斯是我和我合伙人的代表律师
My partner and I were clients of Mike Ross.
我们创立了豌豆空间
We founded Pod Space.
你是麦克斯·劳登
You must be Max Louden.
你怎么知道我不是尼克
How do you know I'm not Nick?
因为迈克说如果你们有人来找我
Because Mike said if one of you ever came to see me,
来的肯定是你
it'd be you.
你不如跟我说说到底是怎么回事
So why don't you tell me what the problem is,
我来帮你解决
and I'll get you out of it.
我也希望事情有这么容易
Oh, I hope it's that easy.
尼克和我做了另一个生意上的投资
Nick and I started another business venture.
筹集了一亿美元启动资金
Raised 100 million to get the thing off the ground.
但账面上只有五千万
I can only account for 50 of it.
五千万不翼而飞
Well, when 50 million is missing,
原因很可能出在挪用公款
the math adds up to embezzlement.
我想到了  可我跟你们说  不是尼克干的
I know that, but I'm telling you, Nick wouldn't do that.
他不会这么对我和公司的
Not to me, and not to the business.
如果他没拿这笔钱  那他就是被骗了
Then if he didn't take it, he got taken.
听我说  我不知道发生了什么
Look, I don't know what happened.
但我知道如果我们解释不了这笔钱的去向
But what I do know is that if we can't account for the money,
如果让别人发现了  我们不仅生意会黄
and anyone finds out, we're not just out of business;
-我们还会入狱的  -相信我  麦克斯
- we're in prison. - Trust me, Max.
我不会让这种事发生的
I'm not going to let that happen.
谢谢
Thank you.
还有  麦克斯
And, Max,
别告诉尼克你和我讲过这件事
don't tell Nick you came to me with this.
我也没这个打算  但我能问下原因吗
Well, I wasn't going to, but do you mind if I ask why not?
我不想让他知道我会去找他
I don't want him to know I'm coming.
我想你也清楚  可是要不就是他干的
I know you already know this, but he's either guilty
想从合伙人那里骗钱
and trying to pin it on his partner,
要不情况反过来
or it's the other way around.
不是那个小伙干的
No way that kid's guilty.
这我可说不好  你也确定不了
I don't know that, and neither do you.
我知道你是经营合伙人
I know you're managing partner,
但你处理你的客户  我处理我的
but you handle your clients, and I'll handle mine.
好吧  但是说清楚  我们刚合并
Hey, fair enough, but just to be clear, we just merged.
我们得留住手里的所有客户
We need to keep every client we've got.
如我所说  罗伯特
Like I said, Robert.
你处理你的客户  我处理我的
You handle your clients, I'll handle mine.
我有个任务要给你
I've got an assignment for you.
早上好  罗伯特  你今天也看上去不错
Oh, good morning, Robert. You look nice today too.
你要是按时上班
Hey, you get to work on time,
我也可以告诉你项链真漂亮
I'll tell you that necklace is pretty all you want.
现在我需要你调查
Right now, I need you to look into
哈维·斯佩克特的一个客户
one of Harvey Specter's clients.
让我理理清楚  我刚干涉完他的一个客户
Let me get this straight. I just finished tussling
结束了跟他的争斗
with the guy over sticking my nose into one of his clients,
现在你又让我干涉
and now you want me to stick my nose
他的另一个客户吗
into another one of his clients?
萨曼莎  他需要你的帮助
Samantha, the man needs your help.
再说  他已经看到了坏处
And besides, he's already seen the bad.
是时候让他尝尝好处了
It's time to show him the good.
再次  我闯入他的领地
And again, what exactly is the good
到底能有什么好处
of me horning in on his territory?
对律所的好处
The good is for the firm.
他现在或许看不到  但他会明白的
He may not see it now, but he will.
-好吧  给我说说  -他有两个年轻人
- Okay, give it to me. - He's got two young bucks.
其中一个参与了见不得人的勾当
One of them is up to something shady.
我不知道是哪一个  但是他特别偏爱
I don't know which one, but he has a soft spot
那个叫麦克斯的小伙子
for the one named Max.
如果麦克斯做错了  他无法做出理性判断
If that guy's wrong, he's not going to see it.
而无论如何  我们不能失去客户
And no matter what, we can't afford to lose the client,
-因为我们刚合并  -没错
- because we just merged. - Exactly.
我就知道留你在身边是有原因的
I knew I keep you around for a reason.
你当然知道
That you do.
那是什么见不得人的勾当
Now, what's the "Something shady"?
-五千万美元失踪了  -听起来不错
- $50 million is missing. - Ooh, that sounds fun.
所以你接手吗
So you're on it?
我不仅接手  罗伯特
Oh, I'm more than on it, Robert.
我都知道该怎么做了
I know exactly what to do.
*看到钱  就愿意留下吃饭*
♪ See the money, wanna stay for your meal ♪
*给你太太再拿块馅饼*
♪ Get another piece of pie for your wife ♪
*所有人都想知道那感觉*
♪ Everybody wanna know how it feel ♪
*所有人都想见见那景象*
♪ Everybody wanna see what it's like ♪
*豆子馅饼我也愿吃  我不在乎*
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie, I don't mind ♪
*我和妹子忙着赚钱*
♪ Me and Missy is so busy, busy making money ♪
*好了*
♪ All right ♪
*退开点  我要跳舞*
♪ All step back, I'm 'bout to dance ♪
诉讼双雄  第八季  第二集
*美钞爵士摇摇摇*
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
你好  你就是唐娜吧  我...
Hi, you must be Donna, I--
让我猜猜
Let me guess.
-萨曼莎·惠勒  -怎么看出来的
- Samantha Wheeler. - What gave it away?
几个地方  最起码的一点是
Several things, not the least of which is you
你在我的办公室埋伏我
ambushing me in my office.
这不是非得是埋伏
Well, it doesn't have to be an ambush.
可能只是友好地打招呼
It could just be a friendly howdy-doo.
如果是这样的话  让我戴上我的牛仔帽
In that case, let me grab my ten-gallon hat,
才更像在打招呼
and help make it that.
你不需要牛仔帽
You don't need a ten-gallon hat.
你只需要在这上面签字
You just need to sign off on this.
萨曼莎  这不是在打招呼
Samantha, this isn't a howdy-doo.
这是一个报销账目请求
This is an expense account request
金额是其他任何人的三倍
three times larger than anyone else's.
在兰德-考德-赞恩律所
Huh, it was only two times bigger
这只是别人的两倍而已
than anyone else's at Rand Kaldor Zane.
-是四倍吧  -你怎么知道的
- Try four times bigger. - How do you know that?
因为知道这个是我的工作
Because it's my business to know that.
我还知道的是我不能签这个
And what I know about this is that I can't sign off on it.
是因为我没有说"请"字吗
Is it because I didn't say please?
因为我不知道它的目的是什么
It's because I don't know that it's for.
-是为了让我完成工作  -这不够具体
- It's for me to do my job. - That isn't very specific.
不  但我以前得到的就是这么多
No, it's not, but it's what I had before,
现在我也需要这么多
and it's what I need now.
你要是想知道细节  去问罗伯特·赞恩
If you want specifics, talk to Robert Zane.
不过他也不知道什么细节
But he doesn't have any, either,
他就喜欢这样
which is how he prefers it.
我不是罗伯特
Well, I'm not Robert.
但既然我也不想出师不利
But since I'm also not trying to get off on the wrong foot,
我会批准一半的金额  能给的就这么多
I will authorize half of this, which is the most we give.
我懂了
I get it.
新人就职  你想确保
The new girl comes in, and you want to make sure
她分得清地位高低
she understands the pecking order.
这不是我的目的
That wasn't my intention.
但你要是这么想
But if that's the way you see it,
比起你对我的了解
that tells me a lot more about you
我倒是更了解你了
than it tells you about me.
终于见到你了  萨曼莎
Good to finally meet you, Samantha.
我也很高兴见到你  唐娜
Good to meet you too, Donna.
哈维  你在这里太好了
Harvey, good, you're here.
是  但不会太久
I am, but not for long.
我得帮迈克的一个老客户
I have to take care of something
处理一些事
for one of Mike's old clients.
没关系  但我现在得跟你谈谈
That's fine, but I need to talk to you now.
你可能不会喜欢我接下来说的...
You may not like what I have to say--
我差点忘了  罗伯特和我签署了文件
Oh, I almost forgot. Robert and I signed the papers
让他接替经营合伙人
for him to take over as managing partner.
-文件在我桌子上  -你们什么
- They're on my desk. - You what?
我知道  我也没想到
I know, I wouldn't have thought it, either,
但是最后发现  我宁愿不做经营合伙人
but as it turns out, I'd rather not be managing partner.
-这不是我想... -路易  帮我个忙
- That's not what I-- - Hey, Louis, do me a favor.
签署文件  然后送去给唐娜  好吗
Sign the papers and drop them off to Donna, will you?
我觉得最好尽快完成这事
I think it's important that we do it as soon as possible
向赞恩表示支持
to show Zane the support
换位思考的话  我也希望能尽快
that I would have wanted if it would have been me.
当然  如果是你的话
Of course, if it would have been you.
-谢谢  路易  -不客气  哈维
- Thanks, Louis. - No problem, Harvey.
我会尽快通知唐娜
I'll get that off to Donna as soon as I can.
-尼克·特纳  -我是
- Nick Turner? - Yes.
-哈维·斯佩克特  -斯佩克特先生你好
- Harvey Specter. - Mr. Specter.
很高兴见到你
It's a pleasure meeting you,
这真是始料未及
but I wasn't aware we had a meeting.
的确  我知道我俩素未谋面
We don't. I know we've never met,
迈克很看重您
but you meant a lot to Mike,
您对我来说自然也很重要
which means you mean a lot to me,
我刚收到一份关于您的提议
and I just got a proposal on your behalf.
史密斯·巴尼愿意为您提供支持
Smith Barney wants to take you public.
真的吗  那真是太好了
You're kidding. That's fantastic.
不仅限于你的主要业务
And it's not just your main business.
还包括您的新项目
They want your new venture too.
我很想表示赞同  但新项目还没有成熟
I'd love to say yes, but the new business isn't ready.
尼克  可不是天天都能有一家高收益的
Nick, it's not often you get a top rate
投行主动到新兴企业找上门来
investment bank knocking on the doors of a fledgling business.
但如果接受
But if we do that,
我们就丧失了最大优势
we won't get the full price of our upside.
如果我告诉你他们愿意
What if I told you they were willing to send over
预支五十万现金以表示信任
500,000 in cash as a good faith advance
以防任何交易过程中的开销呢
against any transaction costs?
-抱歉  你是谁  -萨曼莎·惠勒
- I'm sorry, who are you? - I'm Samantha Wheeler.
哈维的同事
I work with Harvey.
正如我说的  五十万美元
Like I said, half a million dollars.
你只需要提交账簿
All you have to do is send your books over
启动流程  我们就会竭尽全力
to start the process, and we'll get down
让你和你的合伙人赚的盆满钵满
to making you and your partner rich.
感谢你们的盛情  但正如我刚才
Well, that's very generous, but as I was just saying
对哈维说的  我们早就腰缠万贯
to Harvey, we're already rich,
同时我对放弃自己的优势也感到不安
and I don't feel comfortable giving away our upside--
尼克  可别让这只手提箱阻挡了
Nick, don't let this briefcase get in the way
-你的大好前程  -听着
- of a great opportunity-- - Look.
我很感谢你们今天的到来
I appreciate you both coming over,
但我们正值扩建
but we're in the middle of our build out,
所以暂时请回吧
so please, for right now,
我更愿意不作改变
I prefer to keep things like they are.
-这他妈是几个意思  -这家伙可真是淡定
- What the hell was that? - That was one cool cucumber
听上去不错  但事实摆在那里
who sounds pretty good, but couldn't hide the fact
他宁愿断条胳膊都不愿意公开他的账本
that he'd rather cut off his arm than show us his books.
我说  你这样打断我的会面是什么意思
I meant, what were you doing coming into my meeting?
我那是在自我介绍
I was introducing myself,
为了更好的开始
so we could get off on a better foot.
你说过这已经是最好的开始了
I thought you said we got off on the right foot.
我本来是这么觉得  但后来发现这并不是
Well, I think so, but I could tell you didn't.
那我告诉你
Well, let me tell you something.
在我讨论的好好的时候来捣乱
Derailing my meeting when it was going exactly as planned
可不是一个良好的开端
isn't the way to get off on a better foot.
我不知道你讨的什么论
I don't know what meeting you were in,
但那家伙是绝不会给你看账本的
but that man was not going to show you his books.
贿赂他就行了吗
And offering him a bribe is going to get him to?
这不是贿赂  现金是无法追踪的
It wasn't a bribe. It's untraceable cash,
如果他在挪用公款  这钱他是会收的
which if he were embezzling, he would have gone for.
我们丢的可是五千万
We're missing 50 million.
五十万对他来说不过九牛一毛
500,000 isn't going to get him out of his jam.
要是你的前助理
Well, maybe if your ex-assistant
没有冻了我的报销单
hadn't hamstrung me with my expense account,
我可能拿出更多
it would have been more.
萨曼莎  你把唐娜牵连进来
Samantha, you bring Donna into this,
我们是没法有个良好开端的
we're never getting on the right foot.
我的本意不是如此  我...
Look, that wasn't what I meant. I--
够了
That's enough!
我会调查到底
I'm going to get to the bottom of this,
也不需要你的帮助  你怎么就不能
and I don't need your help, so why don't you have
对指挥系统放尊重点
some respect for the chain of command,
别来招惹我的客户呢
and stay away from my clients.
你大爷的
Damn it.
这他娘怎么...
God damn it, what the--
你知道我会用这玩意的  对吧
You know I knew that, don't you?
当然  你只是在检查
Of course you did, you were just testing
机器的结构是否完好
the structural integrity of the machine
还有水和咖啡杯的结构
and the water and the coffee mug.
-没错  -听着  罗伯特
- Precisely. - Listen, Robert.
我不是刚巧过来的
I didn't come in here by accident.
我知道我们对萨曼莎持相反态度
I know we were on opposite sides of the Samantha thing,
但我也知道你打高尔夫  所以也许
but I also know you play golf, and I thought it might be nice
我们可以一起玩玩  认识认识
to get out there and get to know each other.
你其实想说
I think what you really mean
你想给新的执行合伙人留个好印象
is you'd like to impress the new managing partner.
要是我真是这么想的呢
And what if I did?
我告诉你
Now let me tell you something.
到了球场上  只有两件事情可能发生
We get on that course, one of two things is going to happen.
要么你把我气死
Either you're going to piss me off
因为你所向披靡  要么
by being a scratch golfer, or you're going to
我也能给气死  因为你球技太逊了
piss me off by being worse than me.
你想说什么
What's your point?
如果你想给我留下好印象  别考虑高尔夫
You want to impress me, don't do it on a golf course.
给我找一个牛逼的客户来
Do it with a big, fat client.
-哈维  我们得谈谈  -当然
- Harvey, we need to talk. - We sure do.
你是不是给了萨曼莎·惠勒
Did you just give Samantha Wheeler
诺克斯堡的钥匙  她拿了我的手提箱
the keys to Fort Knox to use in my case?
没有  我拒绝了她报销的要求
No, I refused to give her an expense account
要的比诺克斯堡还多  她怎么了吗
even bigger than Fort Knox. Why, what did she do?
她竟然在我跟客户见面的时候要挟我
She tried to hijack my meeting
用的那个装满了现金的手提箱
with a briefcase full of cash.
我猜你可气坏了吧
Let me guess, you didn't like it,
就在她说钱是在我这拿的时候
and that's when she said that she got the money from me.
不  是她说如果你多给她点就能成了
No, she said it would have worked if you'd given her more.
这也就说明了她直接越过我俩找了罗伯特
Which explains why she went over both of our heads to Robert.
难以置信  他给了她三倍的报销金额
I don't believe this. He tripled her expense account.
没错  哈维  我们得搞明白
Yes, he did. Harvey, we need to figure out
我们需要怎么对付这个女人了
what we're going to do about this woman.
我来告诉你我会怎么做
Well, I'll tell you what I'm going to do.
我会告诉罗伯特
I'm going to go tell Robert
如果他不管好他的狗  她就滚蛋
that if he doesn't shorten her leash, she's gone.
或者你可以伸出橄榄枝
Or you could extend the olive branch,
让她和你一起办这个案子
and let her work the case with you.
-我为什么要这么做  -因为有时候
- And why would I do that? - Because sometimes,
和你的朋友拉近关系
it's best to keep your friends close,
但更要亲近我们一无所知的新高级合伙人
and the new senior partner we know nothing about even closer.
你说的都很对
Well, that's all well and fine,
但是我厌倦了对她一无所知
but I am tired of knowing nothing about her.
我也是  所以你用工作让她分心
So am I, so while you're keeping her distracted with work,
我要去把她的老底翻出来
I'm going to go digging in her medicine cabinet.
希拉  我需要跟你谈谈
Sheila, I need to talk to you.
路易  你来早了
Louis, you're an hour early.
我还没把速记垫拿出来呢
I hadn't got my steno pad out yet.
-我知道  但是  -我的天
- I know, but-- - Oh, my God.
你和哈维谈过了  是不是
You talked to Harvey, didn't you?
是的  然后发现哈维想退位
I did, and it turns out that Harvey's stepping down--
那你就是执行合伙人了
And now you're managing partner.
我就知道你能行  你比我想的还要男人
I knew it! You're even more of a man than I thought.
-希拉  -不  利特先生
- Sheila-- - Ah, ah, Mr. Litt.
我不是希拉  而是塞兹小姐
It's not Sheila anymore. It's Miss Sazs,
执行合伙人的秘书
secretary to the managing partner,
而且我准备好被干了
and I am ready to be managed.
希拉  虽然我现在很想上你
Sheila, as much as I would love to manage you right now,
但是现在时机不对
now is not the appropriate time.
你说的没错  时机一点都不合适
You're right. It's not appropriate at all.
就像这里不合适  这里也不合适
Just like this isn't, and this isn't,
-这里也是  -天哪
- and this isn't-- - Whoa, Nelly.
干我  路易  狠狠地干我
Manage me, Louis. Manage the shit out of me.
好啊  你想让我狠狠地干你吗
Okay, you want me to manage the shit out of you?
我现在就来满足你
I'm going to manage the shit out of you.
我不止是路易·利特
And I'm not just Louis Litt.
-我是  -一个笑话
- I'm-- - A joke.
看看他  假装自己是执行合伙人
Look at him, pretending to be managing partner.
真不敢相信他以为我们会让他当
I can't believe he thinks that we would go for it.
难道他不知道执行合伙人首先要是男人吗
Doesn't he know that the first three letters of managing is "Man"?
反正他确实符合"老"这个特点
Well, at least he's got the "Aging" Part down.
说到下面  看起来执行合伙人
Speaking of down, looks like managing partner's
不是他唯一疲软的地方啊
not the only job he'd underperform.
路易
Louis?
-出什么事了吗  -不  没事
- Is something wrong? - No, nothing.
路易  肯定有事  你注意力不在这里
Louis, something's wrong. You're not at attention.
-我知道  我只是  -不  我明白
- I know, I just--I, uh... - Oh, no, of course.
我早该想到的
I should have known.
是这份新工作带来的压力
It's the stress of your new job.
你刚成为执行合伙人
You just became managing partner,
又在工作日中离开岗位
and you're gone in the middle of the workday.
是的
Yes.
-没错  就是这样  -无需多言
- Exactly, that's it. - Then say no more.
回到你的王国
Return to your kingdom.
以后我们有的是时间滚床单
There will be plenty of time for this later.
太好了  你还没走
Oh, good. You're still here.
并不打算久留
Wasn't about to be.
不如我们假装我不在这里
What do you say we both pretend I'm not?
好  怎么了
All right, what's going on?
你和萨曼莎·惠勒打过照面了吗
Have you had a run in with Samantha Wheeler yet?
还没有  不过我猜很快就会了
No, but I take that to mean one's coming.
照她工作的方式  你肯定马上就能见到
The way she operates, you can bet on it.
-她到底是怎么工作的  -任意妄为
- How exactly does she operate? - However the hell she wants.
-难搞  -我也是这个感觉
- Mm-hmm. - My feelings exactly.
所以我决定亲自去调查一下
Which is why I decided to look into
这个"我谁也不听"小姐
little Miss "I don't answer to anyone" myself.
别告诉我你什么也没找到
Don't tell me you came up empty.
比那更糟  一半的人说她来自堪萨斯
Worse, half the people I asked say she's from Kansas.
另一半说来自曼哈顿
The other half, Manhattan.
而且不知怎的  她在相同的两年之内
Somehow, she managed to graduate from an Ivy League,
从一所常春藤学校  一所州校
a state school, and the Sorbonne
和索邦大学毕业
all within the same two years.
甚至有人说她是军情六处的
One guy even says she's MI6,
但那"只是猜测"
but that's "Just a hunch."
所以大家对她的了解没有重合的部分
So you're telling me that no one has the same story
我们无法知晓哪些是真的
and we don't know what's what?
由于人脉比我还广的人只有你
And since the only person with more contacts than me is you,
我希望你能帮我查出点东西来
I was hoping you could help me get some answers.
那你就回家去美美的睡一觉
Then turn around and get a good night's sleep,
因为明天下午
because by tomorrow afternoon,
你会拥有所有这位邦德小妞的资料
you'll have all the answers you need on little Miss James Bond.
你觉得我们是否该来个秘密握手之类的
Do you think we should have a secret handshake or something?
-快走吧  -好的
- Just go. - Okay.
路易  你来这干什么
Louis, what are you doing here?
我们没有预约咨询
We don't have a session scheduled.
我不是来咨询的  我是来勃起的
I'm not here for a session. I'm here for an erection.
-你说什么  -我需要伟哥  斯坦
- A--A what now? - I need a prescription, Stan.
我不管是蓝色小药片
I don't care if it's for the blue pill,
还是给情侣在浴缸里用的
or for the one with the couples in the bathtubs.
我现在就要
I need it now.
路易  不如你告诉我发生了什么
Okay, Louis, why don't you tell me what's going on?
如今我们合并了
Now that we have merged,
希拉认为我该成为执行合伙人
Sheila thinks that I should become managing partner.
我跟她说我会和哈维谈谈
I told her that I would bring it up to Harvey.
但是在我开口以前  哈维告诉我
But before I could do that, he told me that
他已经把律所交给赞恩了
he had already handed the firm over to Zane.
当你告诉希拉这个消息后
And as a result of telling Sheila that,
现在你们的性生活出现了问题
you are now having intimacy issues.
让希拉误以为我已经是执行合伙人后
As a result of letting Sheila think that I'm managing partner,
我就不举了
I can't get it up.
那我必须要告诉你
Then I must tell you,
任何药都解决不了你的问题  路易
a prescription is not going to solve your problem, Louis.
为什么
Why not?
因为你的问题不是血流不畅
Because your issue isn't blood flow.
而是你在欺骗希拉
It's that you are lying to Sheila.
-医生  -路易
- Doc. - Louis.
你不是执行合伙人这件事
How long are you planning to hide the fact
你还要隐瞒多久
that you're not really managing partner?
不知道  两三年吧
I don't know, two to three years?
我爸骗了我妈十年
My father convinced my mother
说他是副总裁
that he was a vice president for a decade.
可以做到的
It can be done.
可能是吧
Be that as it may,
据我说知  杰西卡走后
as I recall, you accepted Harvey becoming
你同意哈维做执行合伙人
managing partner after Jessica left.
我同时意识到
That's when I realized that I didn't want to
自己并不想做执行合伙人
become managing partner.
那你为什么不想告诉希拉你的想法
Then why are you so reluctant to tell Sheila that?
因为她喜欢我掌权的样子
Because she's always been attracted to my power.
我告诉她我不想
I tell her that I don't want to be something
成为她假想的样子
that she wants me to be--
你害怕她不想要你了
You're afraid she will no longer want you.
我不能再失去她  医生
I can't lose her again, doc.
我了解  朋友
I know, my friend.
但真正的强大不是去假装成另一个人
But true power is not pretending to be what you're not.
而是坦然面对自己
It's admitting the truth of who you are.
卡特里娜  能谈谈吗
Katrina, you have a minute?
当然  有什么需要  亚历克斯
Of course, what can I do for you, Alex?
其实我希望你能帮我
I was actually hoping you might be able to
筛选一份名单
help me narrow down a list.
最近我似乎很擅长做这件事
Seems like that's my specialty these days.
什么名单
What kind of list?
这是合并后兰德·考德的客户
These are the clients who stayed with Rand Kaldor after the merger.
没错
That's right.
我想知道哪个客户
And I want to know which one of them
是罗伯特·赞恩最想抢回去的
Robert Zane would like to have back the most.
如果你想知道他最想要回哪个客户
Well, if you want to know who he'd like to have back the most,
那是右舷航空
it's Starboard Airlines.
但如果说你应该抢哪个客户  我不确定
But if you want to know who you should go after, I'm not sure.
我为什么不想要右舷航空呢
Why wouldn't I want to go after Starboard Airlines?
因为他们的代理人是
Because they used to be represented
-萨曼莎·惠勒  -我知道
- by Samantha Wheeler. - I see.
亚历克斯  我不知道你是否了解她
Look, Alex, I don't know how much you know about her,
但如果是我
but I wouldn't want to pick a fight
我可不想找萨曼莎·惠勒的麻烦
with Samantha Wheeler if it were me.
谢谢你的警告
Well, I appreciate the warning,
但如果右舷是罗伯特想要的
but if Starboard's the client Robert would like,
那也是我想要的
that's the client I'm going after.
不管萨曼莎喜不喜欢
Whether Samantha likes it or not.
那祝你好运  但答应我
Then I wish you luck, but do me a favor.
如果她发现了
When she finds out about this,
别把我今天说的告诉她
don't tell her you got it from me.
谢谢你  乔伊  现在你只欠我一个人情了
Thanks, Joe. Now, you only owe me one.
哈维
Harvey.
很可惜  我不会为此道歉
Look. I'm not that big on apologies, so you're not going to get one.
但我考虑了一下  如果你仍想
But I thought about it, and if you're still interested
一起解决这件事  我愿意合作
in working this thing together, I'm good with that.
很好  因为我发现了件事
Good, because I found out
你可能想知道
some things you might want to know.
你仍在调查吗
You kept working on it,
即使我之前告诉你停手
even after I told you to stay out of it?
我也不会为此道歉
I'm not big on apologies, either.
这个就是你最想要的
This is the best you're going to get.
从尼克的银行账单来看
As far as I can tell from Nick's bank statements,
他的支出没做手脚  他没问题
he doesn't spend shit on shit; he's clean.
他的支出可能正常
Well, his spending may be accounted for,
但那五千万的来源有问题
but the original 50 million isn't.
什么意思
What are you talking about?
我查不到任何有关第二笔五千万的来源
I can't find any record of deposits before the second 50 came in.
依我所看
As far as I can tell,
那五千万为项目提供了所有资金
that 50 covered the entire cost of the project.
等一下  他不需要第一笔五千万
Wait a second. He didn't need the first 50.
他需要的是第二笔
He needed the second 50.
没有第一笔他就拿不到第二笔
And he couldn't get the second without saying he had the first.
这说明他误导了投资者
Which means he misrepresented himself to his investors,
这很明显是犯罪
and this is definitely criminal.
该死  我们要告诉麦克斯
Shit, we need to go tell Max,
看看他怎么决定
and run through his options.
哈维  我解决过很多这样的问题
Harvey, I've fixed a lot of situations like this.
我们应该先去找
The first thing we need to do is go to
制造问题的当事人
the guy that caused the problem.
然后再让他把消息透露给麦克斯吗
And give him a chance to implicate his partner?
不可能  应该先去找向我们求助的人
No way, we go to the guy who came to us.
他才是我们的客户
He's our client.
生意是我们的客户
The business is our client.
我接受和你合作
And I'm okay with you working with me on this,
但我不接受你对着我干
but I am not okay with you working it against me.
好吧  那我们明早先去找麦克斯
Okay, we'll go to Max first thing in the morning.
你说的话到明天仍有效吗
I have your word you'll leave it until tomorrow?
我保证
You have my word.
那我们就一起帮他们摆脱这件事
Then let's figure out how to get them out of this.
你是说尼克欺骗了我们的投资商
So you're telling me Nick defrauded our investors?
不  麦克斯  我是说事情看起来是这样
No, Max, I'm telling you that's what it looks like.
我才不管看起来是什么
I don't give a shit what it looks like.
-我需要知道真相  -我们还不知道
- We need to know what it is. - No, we don't.
因为现在只是推测
Because right now, it's conjecture.
如果有证据  我们就有责任通知投资商
We prove it, we have an obligation to inform your investors.
那就通知
So inform them.
如果那么做  你的公司就完了
We do that, your whole company goes out of business.
如果我不说  他们会觉得我参与了诈骗
And if I keep this a secret, they'll think I was in on it.
谈话到此为止  我需要...
This discussion is over, I need--
你需要冷静
What you need is to calm down,
然后听我们说  因为现在有个办法
and listen to us right now, because we have a way out.
是什么
What is it?
合同所示  你有权以30%的溢价
According to your contract, you have the option
买断投资商的股份
to buy out your investors at a 30% return.
他们拿钱走人  我们就当没事发生
They go away happy, and we put this in our rearview mirror.
就算我们有办法弄到这么多钱
And assuming we can even come up with that kind of money,
要是有人先我们一步发现了怎么办
what if someone finds out before we do?
-没人会发现  -这不是答案
- No one's going to find-- - That's not an answer.
-麦克斯  -不
- Max-- - No.
这是尼克的错  不是我的
This is Nick's mistake, not mine,
无辜的人就该去报警
and innocent people go to the police.
听我说  你去揭发他
Listen to me, you turn him in,
这行为就好像急于脱罪的惊弓之鸟
you'll look like a guilty man running scared.
-我确实很害怕  -麦克斯
- I am scared. - Max.
从前你相信迈克  现在我需要你相信我
You used to trust Mike. Now I need you to trust me.
我们给够他们钱  这可能要花上三天
We get these guys paid off; it'll take maybe three days.
然后你就没事了
Then you're fine.
好吧  哈维  我信你
Okay, Harvey. I trust you.
好了  我们按你的方式做了
Okay, we did it your way.
我们和麦克斯谈过了  并且达成了共识
We talked to Max, and we presented a united front.
你最好别是想打破这个共识
You better not be saying you want to divide it now.
我只是想说  还有别的选择
All I'm saying is there's another option.
我们用从真的投资人手里拿到的真钱
We replace the fabricated 50 million with a real 50
替换这五千万假钱  没人会发现的
from an actual investor; no one will ever know.
所以我们只要
Oh, so all we have to do
以骗止骗就能逃脱罪责了吗
is commit fraud to get out of fraud?
说真的  这跟你要做的
And how, exactly, is that any different
到底有什么区别
from what you want to do?
因为我的办法
Because my way is protected
受到法律条文的保护
under the letter of the law.
那我们就得付三成的利息
And we have to pay a 30% return
这事根本不值得
on something that isn't worth it.
不让麦克斯锒铛入狱  我觉得挺值的
Keeping Max out of prison seems worth it to me.
你趁早别跟我吵了
So instead of fighting with me,
还是赶紧想想
why don't you start thinking about
我们去哪儿弄这笔钱吧
where we're going to get that money?
盖文·安德鲁
Gavin Andrews.
你肯定就是想当我新律师的人了
You must be the guy who wants to be my new lawyer.
看来你喜欢直截了当
I see you like to cut to the chase.
你没听说过"时间就是金钱"吗
You ever hear the saying "Time is money"?
我有的是钱
Well, I got a shitload of one,
就是因为我不浪费时间
because I don't waste the other.
那你到底为什么要在
Then why in God's name are you wasting
兰德-考德律所这种公司上耗费时间和金钱呢
either one of them at a firm like Rand Kaldor?
你真的很想趁他们倒霉落井下石是不是
You really want to kick them when they're down, don't you?
这跟他们无关  我问的是你
This isn't about them. This is about you.
你现在四面楚歌  拉瓜迪亚也看不上你
You've got routes under siege. You've lost gates at LaGuardia.
要是你以为听考德的主意  与德尔塔合并
And if you think Kaldor's idea of you merging with Delta
就能解决你的问题
is the answer to your problems,
那我可真是高估了你
then you're not the man I thought you were.
好吧
Okay.
给你个案子  漂亮地解决掉
You get one case; you handle it right,
我的生意就是你的了
you can have my business.
我没有和客户一起入狱的习惯
I'm not in the habit of sharing custody of a client.
不算合伙  因为严格来讲
You're not sharing, because you're not
你不算我的律师  这也不是生意
officially my lawyer, and it's not business;
是私事
it's personal.
你是说我给你处理个私人案件
You're telling me I handle a personal issue for you,
不上台面  我就能拿到你的公司业务
off the record, I get your corporate business?
你为什么这么做
Why would you do that?
因为我需要个信得过的人
Because I need someone
处理公私两边的事物
I can trust to handle both.
在你开口之前  如果你同意的话
Now before you say anything, if you agree to this,
我要你处理  不能找别的律师或者合伙人
you're my guy, not some associate, not another partner.
就是你
You.
好  我加入
Okay, I'm in.
你现在唯一要做的就是告诉我你需要什么
And the only thing left for you to do is tell me what you need.
事实上  我正在离婚  十分棘手
The truth is, I'm in the middle of a nasty divorce,
已经升级到了更加棘手的监护权争夺战
which had led to an even nastier custody battle.
几个孩子  都几岁了
How many kids, and what are their ages?
就一个
Just one.
她185岁了
And she's 185 years old.
哈维  我知道你正要走
Harvey, I know you're on your way out,
-但你得看看这个  -这是什么
- but you got to see this. - What is it?
-真不敢相信  -你要怎么做
- I don't believe this. - What are you going to do?
做我一开始就该做的事
What I should have done in the first place.
把萨曼莎·惠勒狠狠踢出这个案子
Kick Samantha Wheeler the hell off this case.
你到底干了什么
What the hell did you do?
我猜麦克斯给你打电话了吧
I take it Max called you?
没  他给唐娜发了封信
No, he sent Donna a letter
让尼克·特纳正式接任首席执行官
formalizing Nick Turner's transition to CEO
因为麦克斯突然要从公司辞职
since Max is suddenly leaving the company.
其实他是要退居幕后
Actually, he's stepping down
好花更多时间陪陪家人
to spend more time with his family.
我才不在乎他要干什么
I don't give a shit what he's doing.
我想知道你都干了什么
I want to know what you did.
我做了你不会做的事
I did what you wouldn't do.
-保护客户  -胡扯
- Protect the client. - Bullshit.
麦克斯同意履行收购条款了
Max agreed to exercise the buyout clause.
然而他还是联系了一位刑事辩护律师
And yet, he still contacted a criminal defense attorney.
-什么  -他慌了神
- What? - He panicked,
他绝不会守口如瓶的
and he wasn't going to keep his mouth shut,
而我们的客户就会破产倒闭
and our client was going to go out of business.
所以你觉得办法就是逼他辞职吗
So you felt the answer was forcing him out?
我们的目的从始至终都是保护公司
The answer was and always is protect the company.
而你却对保护麦克斯更加上心
And the fact that you were more focused
而不是保护我们的客户
on protecting Max than our client
正因如此  罗伯特才想让我插手此事
is exactly why Robert wanted me to get involved in the first place.
什么
What?
我不是要帮你做得更好
I wasn't trying to make things better with you.
他是想让我盯着你
He wanted me to keep an eye on you.
你没有权利
You had no right
逼迫那个孩子退出自己的公司
to force that kid out of his own company.
-我没有逼他退出  -省省吧你
- I didn't force him out. - Save your bullshit.
你跟我保证过不会耍
You gave me your word that you weren't going to be
这种手段
pulling something like this,
所以要么离我的客户远点
so stay the hell away from my client,
要么下次你再在我背后搞小动作
or the next time you make a move behind my back,
你就得给自己找个新工作了
you'll be finding yourself another job.
你在这儿  今天过得如何  我的国王
Oh, there he is. How was your day, my king?
说实话  并不好
Not great, actually.
或许我可以缓解你的疲劳
Well, maybe I can release your stress.
希拉  等等  我们得谈谈
Sheila, wait. We need to talk.
你今天很累了
Oh, shoot, you've had a hard day.
我们可以回头再谈  现在我
We can talk later. Right now is--
我不是经营合伙人
I'm not managing partner.
什么
What?
我像我说的一样去找哈维了
I went to Harvey, like I said.
在我开口之前
Before I could get the words out,
他就说他已经把这个职位给罗伯特了
he said that he had already offered the job to Robert.
你告诉他你想要这个职位之后他怎么说
Well, what happened when you told him you wanted the job?
我没告诉他我想要
I didn't say I wanted the job.
等等  所以你没有为了你想要的做抗争
Wait, so instead of fighting for what you want,
反而跑来骗我说你已经得到了这个职位
you decided to lie to me about getting it?
-希拉  这么说不公平  -你怎么能对我撒谎
- Oh, Sheila, that's not fair. - How could you lie to me?
我没有  我来是想和你实话实说的
I didn't. I came here to tell you the truth.
但你自己以为我得到了职务
But you thought I already had the job,
而你看起来又那么兴奋
and you seemed so excited about it.
哦  我的天啊
Oh, my God.
这就是为什么你不愿意上床对吧
That's why you couldn't have sex, isn't it?
对
Yes.
对  所以后来我去找利普希茨医生谈了
Yes, so I went to Dr. Lipschitz to talk about it,
你知道他和我说什么吗
and you know what he told me?
他告诉我我应该相信你是爱我的
He told me that I should trust that you love me
而且我可以对你讲实话
and that I can tell you the truth.
而我觉得与其让你的心理医生
And I think instead of letting your therapist
说服你放弃你的梦想
convince you to give up your dream,
不如你昂首挺胸的走进哈维的办公室
maybe you should have marched back into Harvey's office
-夺回属于你的东西  -希拉  拜托了
- to take what's yours. - Sheila, please.
我没有放弃任何东西
I'm not giving up anything.
我不想当经营合伙人
I don't want to be managing partner.
现在你不单是在对我撒谎了
And now you're not only lying to me,
-你还对你自己撒谎  -不  我没有
- you're lying to yourself. - No, I'm not.
我不想当经营合伙人  而你说过你爱我
I don't want managing partner, and you said you love me.
我就是这样的人
Well, this is who I am,
你可以选择是否接受  但我改变不了
and you can either accept that or not, but it's not changing.
你对你哥哥的关心
And it's understandable for you
是可以理解的
to be concerned about your brother.
但是
But...
你为什么坚信他在对自己撒谎呢
why do you believe he's lying to himself?
因为我了解我哥哥
Because I know my brother,
我知道他想要被提拔
and I know he wanted that promotion.
我不能眼睁睁的看着个疯子磨灭他的信心
And I can't stand seeing him not go after it,
从而使他不敢为之一搏
just because some crackpot undermined his confidence.
这个“疯子”具体指的是谁呢
And who exactly is this-- this crackpot?
我可以告诉你是谁  是他的  妈妈
I'll tell you who it is. It's his...mother.
原谅我  但是你不应该称
Uh, forgive me, but wouldn't you refer
他的妈妈为你的妈妈吗
to his mother as your mother?
对  但是
Well, yes, but...
因为  这不是关于我的  我只是在
Well, this isn't about me, I'm trying to--
我的天啊  你是希拉
Oh, my God, you're Sheila.
我不敢相信我之前竟然没看出来
I can't believe I didn't see it before.
抱歉  但是我在电话上告诉过你了
I'm sorry, but I told you on the phone.
在未经过路易允许的情况下见你是不道德的
It is unethical for me to see you without Louis' permission.
我根本不在乎你的道德
I could care less about your ethics.
-你说什么  -别废话了  利普希茨
- Excuse me? - Cut the bullshit, Lipschitz.
路易在赞恩当上经营合伙人之后来找过你
Louis came to see you after Zane got managing partner,
而你非但没有鼓励他把职务夺回来
and instead of encouraging him to take it back,
反而磨灭了他的自信
you undermined his confidence.
你觉得我是那个磨灭他信心的人
It's interesting that you think I'm the one
这真令我觉得好笑  因为
undermining his confidence, because the only times
路易为数不多的几次不在状态的时候
in his life that Louis has been unable to perform
都是因为和你在一起  包括最近一次
have been with you, including most recently
当他想和你讲实话的时候  却又不敢说
when he went to tell you the truth and couldn't
因为他害怕你对他产生什么看法
because he was afraid of how you might view him.
你这他妈是什么意思
What the hell is that supposed to mean?
意思是  或许你觉得你对他很了解
It means, as well as you think you know him,
但他可能对你更了解
he may know you even better.
因为路易不想当经营合伙人
Because Louis does not want to be managing partner.
而比起相信他
And rather than believe him,
你只愿意把他的坦诚当作懦弱
you can only see his admission as cowardice.
但是我不明白
But I don't understand.
他曾经想当过经营合伙人
He wanted managing partner once.
他为什么会改变心意呢
Why would he change his mind now?
因为人不是一成不变的
Because people are not set in stone.
而我猜有什么东西取代了
And I suspect something has replaced
他对经营合伙人的渴望
managing partner as his heart's desire.
-一个孩子  -不  希拉
- A baby. - No, Sheila.
是爱情
Love.
而我想不用我说你也知道
And I don't think you need me to tell you
路易·利特会为了心爱的女人付出一切
Louis Litt would do anything to not lose the woman he loves.
你知道吗  在我来这很久之前就听说过
You know, I had heard about the legendary Donna Paulson
传奇般的人物  唐娜·鲍尔森
long before I even got here.
那倒挺有意思的
Oh, that's interesting.
因为我从没听说过你
Because I've never heard of you.
因为我追求低调  你却想被万众瞩目
Because that's how I want it, but you want to be known.
而且我得告诉你
And I got to tell you,
现实远比传奇故事令人失望
the reality is a lot more disappointing than the legend.
-你说什么  -我和哈维发生了点争执
- Excuse me? - I had a run-in with Harvey
因为你为了麦克斯的事情跑去找了他
because you went running to him about Max.
你说得对  我去了  他有权利知道
You're damn right I did, he deserves to know
有人在他的背后搞小动作
when someone's operating behind his back.
而我有权利去当面告诉他
And I deserve the chance to tell him
究竟发生了什么
what's going on to his face.
所以你是因为我比你抢先一步而生气咯
Oh, so you're upset because I beat you to the punch?
我生气是因为如果你和我有矛盾
I'm upset because if you have any issue with me,
你应该来找我  而不是避开我
you should come to me and not go around me.
就像当初你为了你的报销单
Like how you went around me to Robert
而避开我去找罗伯特那样吗
for your expense account?
所以这才是真正的原因
So that's what this is really about.
不  是因为你对待哈维
No, this is about your behavior with Harvey
对待亚力克斯和我还有很多事的方式
and Alex and me and about 100 other things
你的行为告诉我  你谁都不在乎
that all tell me you don't care about
只在乎你自己
anyone here but yourself.
如果你真的这么认为
If you really think that,
那你真是一点都不了解我
you know nothing about me,
我还要告诉你
and I'll tell you something else.
偷偷地调查我  是不会解决你的疑问的
Secretly digging into me isn't gonna answer your questions.
是的  我知道你一直在偷偷调查我
Yeah, I know you've been doing that too.
如果你足够坦率
And I wouldn't have to
我也犯不着这样
if you'd been upfront about who you are.
你想知道我的事
You want to know something about me?
直接问我就好了
You go ahead and ask.
我怎么相信
And how should I trust
你说的是不是真的
that I'd get a straight answer?
因为我们现在是一条船上的人
Because I am on this team now,
不管你信不信
and whether you believe it or not,
我是把他的利益放在心上的
I've got its best interests at heart.
你真是选了个奇怪的方式表忠心
Well, you got a funny way of showing it.
就我所知  哈维是这家公司的灵魂
Because from where I stand, Harvey is the firm,
但他似乎一点也不支持你
and you don't seem to have his back at all.
喜欢今天的芭蕾表演吗
Are you enjoying the ballet?
当然  你呢
I most certainly am, and how about yourself?
说实话  安德鲁斯夫人
To tell you the truth, Mrs. Andrews,
就算是个二流音乐剧
I wouldn't be less entertained
我也会很享受
if this were a second grade musical.
你是谁  来这干嘛
Who are you, and what are you doing here?
我代表你丈夫来这见你
I'm here on behalf of your husband.
那你现在就可以转身走开了
Then you can turn around, and walk right out
我的律师不在场的情况下  你不能联系我
because you can't contact me without my attorneys present.
如果我是律师的话倒真是这样  但我不是
And that would be true, if I was his lawyer, but I'm not.
那个即将成为我前夫的男人跟你说了什么
And what exactly did my soon-to-be ex-husband tell you?
他告诉我  你到底有什么问题
That whatever issues you had
单纯为了羞辱他  竟把那幅名贵的雷诺阿
led you to take his prized Renoir and loan it
的画拿到纽约大都会艺术博物馆慈善会上放贷
to the Met for the sole purpose of infuriating him.
我没烧掉那破玩意儿已经是他三生有幸了
He's lucky I didn't burn the damn thing.
还是一样  我来是为了说服你把画还回来
All the same, I'm here to convince you to take it back.
怎么才能让你答应我的请求
Now, what will it take to get you to join the team?
波尔多的别墅  无条件免费给我
The Villa in Bordeaux, free and clear.
而且不用我担心交税的问题
And I never want to worry about covering the taxes.
这可不是件小事
That's a big ask.
但那幅昂贵的画我一点也不感兴趣
And it's an expensive painting that I have no interest in,
除非让他在自己的生意伙伴面前看起来像个混蛋
and he can't get back without looking like an asshole
否则我绝不会给他那幅画
to the kind of people he wants to do business with.
怎么了
What?
我算是明白了为什么你不怎么在乎
I can see why you don't really care
你的律师是不是在这儿
if your lawyers are here or not.
成交吗
So we have a deal?
我们要谈谈
We need to talk.
别告诉我哈维去找你了
Don't tell me Harvey came to you.
-他当然来找我了  -他究竟说了什么
- He sure did. - What exactly did he say?
我来不是跟你说他说了什么的
I'm not here to talk about what he said.
我来是为了谈谈你做的事
I'm here to talk about what you're doing.
我做的都是你让我做的事
I'm doing what you asked me to do.
我让你帮他  不是气他
I asked you to help the man, not piss him off.
你让我挽留客户
You asked me to save the client.
这就是挽留客户的代价
This is what it's going to take,
而且你什么时候开始关心我惹谁生气了
and since when do you care if I piss someone off?
自从你让我答应
Since you made me promise to
把你的名字也挂在那堵墙上
put your name up on that wall next.
如果你这么做
Because if you do this,
哈维会尽其所能
Harvey's going to do anything he can
让你的名字永远也挂不到那堵墙上
to stop your name from ever going up on that wall.
你告诉我这么做的  罗伯特
You asked me to do it, Robert.
我已经覆水难收了  现在你让我怎么办
I can't take it back. What do you want me to do now?
让哈维看到我看到的你身上的潜质
Show Harvey what I see in you.
不论以后发生什么  就算到了最紧要的关头
Whatever happens along the way, when push comes to shove,
你也不能让他失望
you will never let him down.
打扰到你了吗
Am I interrupting?
希拉  你来这儿干什么
Sheila, what are you doing here?
我发现
Well, I realized, that, um...
最近你经常来我办公室
that you've been to my office a lot recently,
但我很久没来你办公室了
but I haven't come to yours in a long time.
我知道你来找我
Well, I know it's not the office that you, uh...
不仅仅是因为办公室的事
wanted for me.
这是间完美的办公室  路易
It's the perfect office, Louis.
你是个完美的男人
And you are the perfect man.
如果我让你觉得我心有异议
And I'm sorry if I made you feel
我想说声抱歉
like I ever thought differently.
所以我不想当执行合伙人
So you don't think I'm weak
你也不会觉得我软弱无能
for not wanting to be managing partner?
不  我不这么想
No, I don't.
我失望的原因
And the reason I got so upset
并不是因为我觉得你软弱无能
wasn't because I think you're weak.
而是因为我觉得哈维和罗伯特·赞恩
It's that I thought Harvey and Robert Zane
不听你说完你的话是他们有眼无珠
didn't even value you enough to hear you out.
-他们确实有眼无珠  -除此之外
- No, they didn't. - And on top of that,
你当时那么想进去  做一番自己的事业
you were so excited to go in there and make your case.
-是的  -所以到底怎么了
- Yes, I was. - So what happened?
-我进去和哈维见面  -然后呢
- I went in to see Harvey. - And what?
他连一天时间都没给我
He didn't even give me the goddamn time of day.
路易  我不是来激励你的
Okay, Louis, I'm not trying to get you worked up.
因为我要告诉你  我不需要你
Because I'm telling you, I don't need you
成为执行合伙人
to be managing partner.
我也不需要  但我想要的
No, and I don't need it either, but what I do need
是他们能以基本礼节对待我
is to be given the common courtesy
让我觉得我被平等对待了
of being treated like an equal.
那你接下来要怎么办
So what are you going to do?
我要做的第一件事
Well, the first thing I'm going to do
就是马上回家
is go home right now and
做我那天没能做成的事
do what I couldn't do the other day.
那明天一早  我就去告诉罗伯特·赞恩
Then tomorrow, first thing, I'm going to go tell Robert Zane
还有哈维·斯佩克特墙上有三个名字
and Harvey Specter that there are three names on that wall,
其中一个需要得到更多尊重
and one of them deserves some goddamn respect.
好
Okay.
收到你要求在这里见面的神秘短信了
I got your mysterious message about meeting in here.
怎么了
What's going on?
你找到什么萨曼莎的什么信息了吗
Did you find something out about Samantha?
-她找到的  -你来干什么
- She did. - What are you doing here?
她来是因为和你一样
She's here because like you,
我收集了不少矛盾信息
I got a lot of conflicting information.
她是唯一一个
She's the only person I know
我知道和萨曼莎正面交锋过的人
that's had direct experience with Samantha.
那说吧
Well?
跟她认识的人不是爱她就是怕她
People either love her or are afraid of her.
但所有用过她的人在这件事上都一致
But anyone who's ever used her says the same thing.
她一点也不必他们差
She is as good as they come.
战场上见面  他们不想与她为敌
And when the chips are down, you want her in your corner.
那现在我们是敌是友
Do you think she's in our corner?
我想那取决于
I guess that depends on whether or not
罗伯特和哈维是敌是友了
Robert and Harvey are in the same corner.
我知道你现在没这个心情
I know you're not in the mood.
我只是想解释一下麦克斯·劳登的事
I just want to explain what happened with Max Louden.
没必要解释  就是你勒索了他
I know what happened. You blackmailed him.
-我没有  -那你干什么了
- I did not blackmail him. - Then what did you do?
我问自己  一开始尼克到底是怎么
I asked myself, how the hell did Nick pull this shit
骗到麦克斯的  他可不是白痴
on Max in the first place? He's not an idiot.
他肯定是分神了
He must have been distracted.
有区别吗
What difference does that make?
区别在于  麦克斯分神
The difference is, Max was distracted
是因为他妹妹得了癌症
with his sister who has cancer.
所以我找了关系  让她吃了官司
So I pulled some strings, got her into a trial,
所以他就乖乖下台了
and he was more than happy to step down.
好吧  所以我想错了你让他放手的方式
Okay, so you didn't boot him out the way I thought.
那我们怎么防止尼克·特纳
What's going to stop Nick Turner
再让我们陷入这个境地呢
from putting us in this position again?
用你的方式又能怎么做
What would have stopped him your way?
麦克斯就能做到
Max would've.
所以我才想帮他
That was the reason I wanted to back him.
这不是麦克斯  但也许也有用
Well, this isn't Max, but maybe it will do.
我猜猜  你想做这件事
Let me guess, you want to be the one to do it.
不  我不想  他是你的委托人  你去做
No, I don't. He's your client; you do it.
当然除非  你需要我帮忙
Unless, of course, you need me to hold your hand.
我比较确定我能处理
I'm pretty sure I can take care of this myself.
干得好  萨曼莎
This is nice work, Samantha.
我只是想融入团队
I just want to be part of the team.
这里真的开始团结起来了
You know, the place is really starting to come together.
和你上次看到的也没什么区别
Doesn't look any different than the last time you saw it.
我知道  我才发现你是个骗术大师
I know, I just figured you're a bullshit artist,
所以也许你会喜欢
so you'd probably appreciate
别人拍拍你的马屁
a little smoke blown up your ass.
-什么  -好吧  听你的
- Excuse me? - Okay, have it your way.
我们就别胡扯了  直接谈谈
We'll cut the bullshit and get to the part
你诈骗投资人出了这里的钱的事吧
where you defrauded your investors to pay for this place.
-我没有  -在你费劲
- I didn't-- - And before you even
骗我前
lie to me about it,
不如换成感谢我救了你吧
why don't you start thanking me for getting you out of it?
-你给我找到投资了  -是  当然  为此
- You got me new funding? - I did.Of course, to do that,
我就得让银行知道你的首次公开募股计划
I had to let the bank inon your IPO plans.
我没有首次公开募股计划
I don't have any IPO plans.
你现在有了
You do now.
我懂了
I get it.
一旦我们公开交易  我就有了董事会
Once we're publicly traded, I'll have a board of directors,
他们就能看到我的账本了
and they'll have full access to my books.
所以希望你很享受这次违法
Which means I hope you enjoyed breaking the law once,
因为没有下次了
because it's never going to happen again.
要是我拒绝  然后解雇你呢
And what if I say no, and then I fire you?
那你就会入狱
Well, then you end up in prison,
本来做这种事99%也都是这个下场
which happens 99% of the time in cases like this anyway.
那剩下的1%呢
What happens the other 1% of the time?
就在你面前  相信我  尼克
You're looking at him. And trust me, Nick.
有我这样能力的人  最好不要当敌人
A guy who can do what I did, you want him on your team.
再联系
I'll be in touch.
哈维  你看起来像那只吃了金丝雀的猫
Harvey, you look like the cat that ate the canary.
不如说是办妥了事的男人
More like the man who took care of business.
-办妥了  -是萨曼莎办妥的
- So you got it done? - Samantha got it done.
-那我们和好了吗  -这意味着下次
- Does that mean we're good? - It means the next time
你再担心我处理委托人事务的方式时
you're worried about how I handle my clients,
当面告诉我
tell me to my face.
没问题
Fair enough.
那萨曼莎呢  和她和好了吗
And how about Samantha? You good with her?
还不能说好到不行
I wouldn't go throwing a ticker tape parade just yet,
但我承认  我开始看到她的能力了
but yeah, I admit, I'm starting to see what you see in her.
我别无他求
Well, that's all I was hoping for.
也就是说  我可以告诉你为什么了
Which means now, I can tell you why I was hoping it.
怎么了  你还有什么没告诉我的
What's going on? What haven't you told me?
下一个当冠名合伙人的是她
That her name goes up on the wall next.
要想说什么先等等  我保证了的
And before you say anything, I gave her my word.
-罗伯特  -不管
- Listen, Robert-- - Whatever it is
你要说什么  都得等等
you're about to say, it's going to have to wait,
因为我们三个现在必须要
because the three of us are going to have a little talk
谈一件重要的事
about something right the hell now.
-怎么了  路易  -我告诉你怎么了
- What's going on, Louis? - I'll tell you what it is.
你们俩自己决定了谁要管理公司
The two of you decided who's running this firm
根本没经过我同意
without including me in the conversation.
你说什么呢  你签了协议的
What are you talking about? You signed the agreement.
你起草的协议
The agreement that you drew up,
就觉得我完全不会有意见
and just expected me to be okay with.
你是说你想当经营合伙人吗
You're saying that you want to be managing partner?
不  罗比
No, Robbie.
但你当然不知道  因为你就没问过我
But you wouldn't know that, because you never asked,
我拒绝因为我的名字在最后
and I will not be the third wheel
就被你们架空
just because my name comes last.
没人想架空你  路易
No one thinks of you as a third wheel, Louis.
是吗
Oh, really?
因为要不是我你也不会在这里
Because you wouldn't be here if it weren't for me,
要不是我  你也不会有律所了
and you wouldn't have a firm at all if it weren't for me.
我救了你们的小命
I saved both your ----ing asses,
但你们不但没感谢我
and not only didn't you think to thank me,
而且就我感觉  你们都不记得我干了这些
as far as I can tell, you didn't even clock what I did.
我和你们一样都是合伙人
Now, I am a partner just as much as you,
我已经受够不停提醒你们了
and I am done having to remind you of that.
所以下次需要做决定  两位
So the next time there's a decision to be made, guys,
你们最好在那儿给我留个位子
you better pull up a seat for me at that table,
否则我发誓  我就砸了它
or I swear to God, I will break the whole goddamn thing in two.
有问题吗
Any questions?
没有  路易  没问题
No, Louis, no questions.
很好
Good.
看来你不是唯一一个
Looks like you're not the only one
我需要说服的人了
I'm going to have to make good with.
但是他冲进来前
But what were you talking about
你在说什么
before he came storming in here?
不重要了  重要的是
It doesn't matter, what matters is
你要怎么处理路易的事
what are we going to do about Louis?
-孩子真美  -因为妈妈美
- Beautiful girls. - They take after their mother.
我听说他们爸爸
Hm, well, I hear their father
正要追右舷航空公司
is going after Starboard Airlines.
-从哪听说的  -我就当你承认了
- Where'd you hear that? - I'll take that as a yes.
-要是没错呢  -换做我  我就放弃
- And what if I am? - If I were you, I'd stop.
换做我  我会说你之所以这么说
And if I were me, I'd say you're only saying that
是因为他们曾经是你的委托人
because they used to be your client,
你觉得他们现在成为我的委托人
and you're not going to like how it looks
你会没面子
when they become mine.
我这么说是因为盖文·安德鲁
I'm saying that because Gavin Andrews
不只是表面上那样
is a hell of a lot more than meets the eye,
不值得费那么多麻烦
and the guy isn't worth the trouble.
什么麻烦
What kind of trouble?
这么说吧  我觉得有你的黑历史放在那
Let's just say I would have thought a guy with your history
我会以为你会更小心
would want to be more careful
在与谁合作上更谨慎些的
about who he gets into bed with.
你调查我的背景干什么
What the hell are you doing looking into my history?
我做的是你该对他做但没做的事
I'm doing what you should be doing with him.
那告诉我你指的是什么事
Then tell me what you're talking about,
否则离开我的办公室
or get out of my goddamn office
我还有委托人要签
because I've got a client to sign.
抱歉打扰  亚历克斯  祝你好运
Sorry to bother you, Alex. Good luck with that client.
-这才是我的雄狮  -你穿衣服了吗
- There's my lion. - Are you naked under there?
这是做爱专用睡衣  不是吗
This is my sex robe, isn't it?
当然了  化成灰我都认得
Yeah, of course, I would recognize that anywhere,
但是希拉  这是刮得什么风
but Sheila, where is this coming from?
这阵风
It's coming from right there.
我们记得你
哈维  罗伯特
-天哪  他们听了我的话  -是你的咆哮
- Oh, my God, they heard me. - They heard you roar.
-因为你是头雄狮  -我确实是  对吧
- Because you are a lion. - I am, aren't I?
没错
Yes, you are.
而且被记住的不只是你
And you should know that you're not the only one with a clock.
院长今天也表扬你了  对吗
The dean gave you a clock today, too?
不是那个  是我的生物钟
Not that kind of clock. I have an internal clock.
希拉  你是在说我认为你在说的吗
Sheila, are you saying what I think you're saying?
是的  因为当我说你是我的
Yes, I am, because when I told you
完美伴侣时  路易·利特  我是认真的
you're the perfect man, Louis Litt, I meant it.
我想跟你要个完美的孩子
And I want to make a perfect baby with you.
-你确定吗  -确定
- Are you sure? - Absolutely.
我不想只是停止预防措施
And I don't want to just pull the goalie.
我想努力尝试
I want to start trying.
我想现在就开始尝试
And I want to start trying right now.
太完美了
This is incredible.
-我们还是可以玩点刺激的吧  -当然
- Can we still do it dirty? - Of course.
为什么不行
Why couldn't we do it dirty?
因为我不希望儿子那么想我们
Because I don't want our son to think of us that way.
路易  我们的儿子会是个小利特
Louis, our unborn son will be a Litt.
他会尊重我们玩刺激游戏
He'll respect us for being dirty.
一点没错  我们想怎么刺激都行
You're 100% right, we can be as filthy as we want.
-我去拿香蕉  -你是疯了吗
- I'll get the bananas. - What are you, crazy?
你是要当妈妈的人
You're going to be the mother of my child.
我去拿
I'll get the bananas.
赞恩·斯佩克特·利特
你要真的按键
You know, the elevators come a lot faster
电梯才能快一点
when you actually call them.
我只是在思考
I was just thinking.
我想告诉你  我已经停止
Well, I wanted to let you know that I finished
调查萨曼莎了
checking on Samantha.
然后呢
And?
就我看  虽然她不是圣人
As far as I can tell, she may not be Mother Teresa,
但她对团队很有价值
but she's an asset to the team.
我想那取决于这是谁的团队
I guess that depends on who the team is.
-什么意思  -赞恩许诺了萨曼莎
- What do you mean? - Zane promised Samantha
接下来让她的名字上墙
she'd be the next name partner.
你跟他说你也保证了亚历克斯了吗
And did you tell him that you made the same promise to Alex?
没有
No, I didn't.
哈维  你不能让他们同时上墙
Harvey, you can't put them both up at the same time.
这会让他们二人的升职都贬值
It'll dilute the promotion for both of them.
我知道
I know.
那你什么打算
So what are you going to do?
我要做杰西卡会做的事
I'm going to do what Jessica would.
我要回家  给我倒杯酒
I'm going to go home, make myself a drink,
然后想想怎么得到我想要的
and figure out how to get my way.